movado.com 2019-12-13

# Movado Privacy Policy

### MOVADO GROUP GLOBAL PRIVACY POLICY

Effective Date: 24 October 2018

We at Movado Group, Inc. (“MGI”) along with our subsidiaries and affiliates (collectively, “Movado Group”), respect your concerns about privacy.

This Global Privacy Policy will inform you about the type of information we collect about our consumers, how we use and look after that information, and your privacy rights. If you have any questions about this Global Privacy Policy, please [_Contact us_](mailto:privacy@movadogroup.com).

This website is not intended for children, and we do not knowingly collect data relating to children.

This Global Privacy Policy is provided in a layered format so you can click through to the specific areas set out below. If you would like to download a pdf version of this policy [click here](https://www.movado.com/on/demandware.static/-/Sites-MovadoUS-Library/default/dw298eccc5/content-assets/Global%20Privacy%20Policy%20en%20Eff%202018%2010-24.pdf).

### 1\. IMPORTANT INFORMATION AND WHO WE ARE

We may collect information about you in various ways, such as when you provide it at our stores, on our websites, through apps, “smart” wearable devices and social media channels, at our events, through sweepstakes and promotions, in response to surveys, via text messages, or on the telephone. In addition, when you visit our websites, open our emails, use our apps or “smart” wearable devices, or interact with Movado Group related tools, widgets, or plug-ins, we may collect certain information by automated means, such as cookies, web beacons, and web server logs. In certain circumstances, we also collect information from third-party service providers and platforms or third parties may share with us information they have gathered about you. By engaging with us you acknowledge the terms of this Global Privacy Policy and the use and disclosure of your personal data as set out in this policy.

This Global Privacy Policy aims to give you information on how Movado Group collects and processes your personal data.

It is important that you read this Global Privacy Policy together with any other privacy notice or fair processing notice we may provide on specific occasions when we are collecting or processing personal data about you so that you are fully aware of how and why we are using your data. This Global Privacy Policy supplements the other notices and is not intended to override them.

CONTROLLER

This Global Privacy Policy is issued on behalf of the Movado Group of companies, so when we mention “Movado Group,” “we,” “us,” or “our” in this Global Privacy Policy, we are referring to the relevant company in the Movado Group of companies responsible for processing your data. Please see _Movado Group Companies that Process and Share Personal Data_ for details about the different legal entities that are part of Movado Group and which Movado Group entity is the controller for this website.

CONTACT DETAILS

If you have any questions about this Global Privacy Policy, including any requests to exercise your legal rights, please email us at [_PRIVACY@MOVADOGROUP.COM_](mailto:privacy@movadogroup.com). Please understand that due to time differences and other factors we may not be able to respond to your query immediately; we will, however, respond as quickly as we can and within any legal requirements. You also may write to a specific Movado Group entity, Attn: Legal Department, using the mailing information available here _Movado Group Companies that Process and Share Personal Data_.

CHANGES TO THIS GLOBAL PRIVACY POLICY AND YOUR DUTY TO INFORM US OF CHANGES

This version was last updated effective on the date set forth at the top of this document. We may update our Global Privacy Policy periodically. For significant changes, we will notify you by posting a prominent notice on our website indicating at the top of the notice when it was most recently updated.

It is important that the personal data we hold about you is accurate and current. Please update your account or [_Contact us_](mailto:privacy@movadogroup.com) if your personal data changes during your relationship with us.

THIRD-PARTY LINKS

For your convenience and information, our websites and apps may provide links to non-Movado Group websites, apps, plug-ins, and services. Clicking on those links or enabling those connections may allow third parties to collect or share data about you. Similarly, our products and services may be made available to you through third-party platforms (such as providers of app stores) or through other third-party channels. Movado Group does not control these third-party sites and is not responsible for their privacy practices. We encourage you to read the privacy policy of every site and channel you visit.

### 2\. THE DATA WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU

Personal data, or personal information, means any information about an individual from which that person can be identified. It does not include data where the identity has been removed (anonymous data) or is otherwise not ascertainable.

We may collect, use, store, and transfer different kinds of personal data about you, which we have grouped together as follows:

  * **Identity Data** includes first name, last name, username or similar identifier, and title.
  * **Contact Data** includes first name, last name, billing address, delivery address, email address, and mobile or other telephone numbers.
  * **Payment Data** includes bank account and payment card details, expiration date, authorization number or security code, and billing address.
  * **Transaction Data** includes Contact Data, Payment Data, and details about products and services you have purchased from us.
  * **Customer Service Data** includes service inquiries, comments, and warranty and repair history.
  * **Technical Data** includes internet protocol (IP) address, your login data, browser type and version, time zone setting and location, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system and platform, and other technology on devices you use to access this website. For further details, see _Cookies and Other Automated Means_.
  * **Profile Data** includes username or similar identifier, password, date of birth, gender, marital status, demographics, Transaction Data, and your interests, preferences, feedback, and survey responses .
  * **Usage Data** includes information about how you use our website, products, and services.
  * **User Content** includes photographs, comments, and other content you provide.
  * **Marketing and Communications Data** includes your preferences in receiving marketing from us and our third parties.
  * **Friends Data** includes contact information you provide about friends or other people you would like us to contact.

Please keep in mind that many of the data elements mentioned above do not by themselves constitute personal data but instead only constitute personal data when combined with other data elements. For example, demographics data, Usage Data, and details about products and services you purchase from us do not constitute personal data unless combined with Identity Data or other data that connects such information to your identity.

We also collect, use, and share **Aggregated Data** such as statistical or demographic data for any purpose. Aggregated Data may be derived from your personal data but is not considered personal data in law as this data does not directly or indirectly reveal your identity. For example, we may aggregate your Usage Data to calculate the percentage of users accessing a specific website feature. However, if we combine or connect Aggregated Data with your personal data so that it can directly or indirectly identify you, we treat the combined data as personal data which will be used in accordance with this Global Privacy Policy.

When permissible, we may collect any **Special Categories of Personal Data** about you (this includes details about your race or ethnicity, religious or philosophical beliefs, sex life, sexual orientation, political opinions, trade union membership, information about your health and genetic and biometric data). We do not collect any information about criminal convictions and offenses. We do not seek to collect any Special Categories of Personal Data in respect of residents of the European Economic Area (“EEA”) (which includes the member states of the European Union plus Iceland, Lichtenstein and Norway) and Switzerland or under other circumstances in which the General Data Protection Regulation applies (please see _Bases for Using Your Personal Data_, below).

When you provide us with User Content or other data, please do not include any of these Special Categories of Personal Data, especially with reference to another person. If we become aware that you have provided any of this type of information to us when submitting User Content, we will either delete the information from our records or communicate with you concerning your intentions for our use of the information you provided.

When we need to collect personal data by law or under the terms of a contract we have with you, and you fail to provide that data when requested, we may not be able to perform the contract we have or are trying to enter into with you (for example, to provide you with goods or services). In this case, we may have to cancel a product or service you have with us, but we will notify you if this is the case at the time.

### 3\. HOW WE COLLECT YOUR PERSONAL DATA

We use different methods to collect data from and about you, including through:

  * **Direct interactions.** You may give us your Identity, Contact, Payment, Transaction, Customer Service, Profile, User Content, and/or Marketing and Communications Data by filling in forms or by corresponding with us by mail, telephone, email, social media, or otherwise. This includes personal data you provide when you: 
    * Create an account;
    * Seek to purchase our products;
    * Apply for our services (such as warranty or after-sales service);
    * Subscribe to our newsletter;
    * Request marketing to be sent to you;
    * Enter a competition, promotion or survey;
    * Interact with us on social media; or
    * Give us some feedback.
  * **Automated technologies or interactions.** As you interact with our website, apps, social media platforms, physical stores, and “smart” watches, we may automatically collect Technical, Profile, and/or Usage Data about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns. We collect this personal data by using cookies, server logs, location-sensing technology, and other similar technologies. We may also receive Technical, Profile, and/or Usage Data about you if you visit other websites employing our cookies. Please see _Cookies and Other Automated Means_ for further details.
  * **Third parties or publicly available sources.** We may receive personal data about you from various third parties and public sources, including the following: 
    * Identity and Contact Data from publicly available sources;
    * Contact, Payment and Transaction Data from payment processor and fraud detection and prevention companies;
    * Identity and/or Contact Data from friends or people you know and who have asked us to contact you;
    * Technical Data from analytics providers like Google;
    * Technical Data from search information providers;
    * Identity, Contact, Profile, Usage, User Content, and/or Friends Data from social media channels like Facebook, Instagram, Pinterest, and Twitter.
    * Identity, Contact, Profile, and/or Usage Data from advertising networks and marketing lists; and
    * Identity, Contact, and/or Profile Data from marketing insights companies like Experian.

### 4\. BASES FOR USING YOUR PERSONAL DATA

We will only use your personal data when the law allows us to do so. Most commonly, we will use your personal data in the following circumstances:

  * Where we need to perform the contract we are about to enter into or have entered into with you.
  * Where it is necessary for our legitimate interests (or those of a third party, where permissible).
  * Where we need to comply with a legal or regulatory obligation.

Generally, we do not rely on consent as a legal basis for processing your personal data. However, we strive to provide you with choices regarding certain personal data uses, particularly around marketing and advertising. You can change those choices at any time by clicking the “unsubscribe” link on the communication sent to you or by [_Contacting us_](mailto:privacy@movadogroup.com). When you unsubscribe we will stop sending you direct marketing communications but may continue using your personal data for other purposes for which a different lawful basis for processing exists. If you choose to provide us with your email address to receive our newsletter or other direct marketing materials, we will not share that information with unaffiliated entities for those third parties’ own purposes, although as described below we may share that information with unaffiliated third parties to help facilitate and improve our own communications with you.

PURPOSES FOR WHICH WE WILL USE YOUR PERSONAL DATA

We may use your personal data and other information for any purpose permitted by law.

On 25 May 2018, the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) promulgated by the European Union came into effect. The GDPR limits the legal bases upon which we may collect and use personal data and requires us to explain which legal bases we rely on for the processing of data when the GDPR applies.

We have therefore set out below in table format (the “GDPR Table”) a description of the ways we plan to use your personal data and which of the legal bases we rely on to do so if and when the GDPR applies, including whenever the subject of the personal data is a resident of the EEA or Switzerland. In the GDPR Table “legitimate interests” means our interest in conducting and managing our business to enable us to give you the best products and services and the best and most secure experience and to grow our business. Although many things go into making this happen, to help you better understand what our legitimate interests are we have identified in the GDPR Table certain examples. Since we do not seek to collect any Special Categories of Personal Data when the GDPR applies, the GDPR Table does not include examples of the use of Special Categories of Personal Data.

Note that under the GDPR we may process your personal data for more than one lawful ground depending upon the specific purpose for which we are using your data. Please [_Contact us_](mailto:privacy@movadogroup.com) if you need details about the specific legal ground we are relying on to process your personal data where more than one ground has been set out in the GDPR Table below.

**Purpose/Activity under GDPR**

**Type of data**

**Lawful basis under GDPR for processing**

To register you as a new customer / to create and manage your user account

  1. Identity
  2. Contact
  3. Payment
  4. Transaction

  1. Performance of a contract with you
  2. Necessary for our legitimate interests (to keep our records updated, to service our consumers and optimize the consumer experience)

To verify your identity

  1. Identity
  2. Contact
  3. Payment
  4. Transaction
  5. Technical

  1. Performance of a contract with you
  2. Necessary to comply with a legal obligation
  3. Necessary for our legitimate interests (to protect against identity theft and to prevent fraud and other unlawful activity, claims, and other liabilities)

To process and deliver your order including: 

  1. Manage payments, fees, and charges
  2. Reduce credit risk
  3. Collect and recover money owed to us

  1. Identity
  2. Contact
  3. Financial
  4. Transaction
  5. Marketing and Communications

  1. Performance of a contract with you
  2. Necessary to comply with a legal obligation
  3. Necessary for our legitimate interests (to keep our records updated, to protect our business and shareholders, to study how customers use our products/services)

To provide product and services offerings to you

  1. Identity
  2. Contact
  3. Transaction
  4. Profile
  5. Usage
  6. Technical
  7. Marketing and Communications
  8. Friends

Necessary for our legitimate interests (to study how customers use our products/services, to develop them, to grow our business, and to inform our marketing strategy)

To determine warranty coverage and provide customer services, including responding to your inquiries

  1. Identity
  2. Contact
  3. Transaction
  4. Customer Service

  1. Performance of a contract with you
  2. Necessary to comply with a legal obligation
  3. Necessary for our legitimate interests (to improve our products/services, to grow our business)

To respond to complaints of injuries and/or administer product recalls

  1. Identity
  2. Contact
  3. Transaction
  4. Customer Service

  1. Performance of a contract with you
  2. Necessary to comply with a legal obligation
  3. Necessary for our legitimate interests (to improve our products/services)

To perform accounting, auditing, and other internal functions

  1. Transaction
  2. Customer Service
  3. Usage

  1. Necessary to comply with a legal obligation
  2. Necessary for our legitimate interests (for running and growing our business)

To comply with and enforce public company reporting and other legal requirements, relevant industry standards, contractual obligations, and our policies

  1. Transaction
  2. Customer Service
  3. User Content

  1. Necessary to comply with a legal obligation
  2. Necessary for our legitimate interests (for running and growing our business)

To enable you to partake in a prize draw, competition, or sweepstakes or to complete a survey

  1. Identity
  2. Contact
  3. Profile
  4. Usage
  5. Marketing and Communications

  1. Performance of a contract with you
  2. Necessary for our legitimate interests (to study how customers use our products/services, to develop them, and to grow our business)

To operate, evaluate, improve, administer and protect our business, this website, and our apps and other services (including troubleshooting, data analysis, testing, system maintenance, support, reporting and hosting of data)

  1. Identity
  2. Contact
  3. Technical
  4. Profile
  5. Usage

Necessary for our legitimate interests (for running our business, to study how customers use our products/services, for provision of administration and IT services, network security, to prevent fraud, and in the context of a business reorganization or group restructuring exercise, to inform our marketing strategy)

To deliver relevant website, app, social media, and other digital content and advertisements to you and to measure or understand the effectiveness of the advertising we serve to you

  1. Identity
  2. Contact
  3. Profile
  4. Usage
  5. Marketing and Communications
  6. Technical

Necessary for our legitimate interests (to study how customers use our products/services, to develop them, to grow our business, and to inform our marketing strategy)

To use data analytics to improve our website, apps, products/services, marketing, customer relationships, and experiences

Necessary for our legitimate interests (to define types of customers for our products and services, to keep our websites, apps, devices and tools updated and relevant, to develop our business, and to inform our marketing strategy)

To make suggestions and recommendations to you about goods or services that may be of interest to you

  1. Identity
  2. Contact
  3. Technical
  4. Usage
  5. Profile

Necessary for our legitimate interests (to develop our products/services and to grow our business)

To market and advertise our products and services

  1. User Content
  2. Identity
  3. Friends

Necessary for our legitimate interests (to inform our marketing strategy, to develop our customer base, to grow our business)

INTEREST-BASED ADVERTISING

On our websites, apps, social media pages, and other tools and when you use one of our “smart” wearable devices or visit one of our physical stores, we may collect information about your online activities and geolocation information for use in providing you with advertising about products and services tailored to your individual interests.

If automatic technologies have been enabled, you may see certain ads on other websites because we engage third-party ad buying networks. Through such buying networks, we can target our messaging to users through demographic, interest-based, and contextual means. We can track your online activities over time by collecting information through automated means, including through the use of third-party cookies, web server logs, pixels and web beacons. The networks use this information to show you advertisements that may be tailored to your individual interests. The information our ad networks may collect on our behalf includes data about your visits to websites that serve Movado Group advertisements, such as the pages or advertisements you view and the actions you take on the websites. This data collection takes place both on our websites and on third-party websites that participate in these ad networks. This process also helps us track the effectiveness of our marketing efforts.

To learn how to opt-out of some or all of this ad network interest-based advertising, please visit the consumer opt-out page at [_HTTP://WWW.ABOUTADS.INFO/CHOICES/_](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/). For more information about our use of automatic technologies and third-party analytics services, see _Cookies and Other Automated Means_.

### 5\. SHARING YOUR PERSONAL DATA

We do not disclose personal data we collect about you, except as described in this Global Privacy Policy.

We may share your personal data within the Movado Group of affiliated companies worldwide. See _Movado Group Companies that Process and Share Personal Data_ for a list of Movado Group companies that process and share personal data.

We also may share your personal data with external third parties, including service providers who perform services on our behalf based on our instructions. We do not authorize these service providers to use or to disclose the data except as necessary to perform services on our behalf or to comply with legal requirements. Examples of these service providers include entities that process credit card payments, manage and reduce our credit risk, verify information, fulfill orders, and provide web hosting, analytics, and marketing services.

Where permitted by law, we may share your personal data with other third parties for those parties’ own purposes, such as to offer products or services that may interest you. For example, as described in _Cookies and Other Automated Means_, we allow carefully-selected third parties to set cookies during your visit to our website that enables them to provide you with relevant messaging on other websites. However, as explained above, we will not share your email address with unaffiliated parties for their own direct marketing purposes. You may tell us that you do not wish any other personal data to be shared with third parties for those parties’ own purposes by [_Contacting us_](mailto:privacy@movadogroup.com).

In addition, we may disclose information about you (i) if we are required to do so by law or legal process, (ii) to law enforcement authorities or other government officials, (iii) when we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to prevent physical harm or financial loss, or in connection with an investigation of suspected or actual fraudulent or illegal activity, (iv) to third parties to whom we may choose to sell, transfer, or merge parts of our business or our assets, and/or (v) to new owners who have acquired or have merged with our business.

### 6\. INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS

As set forth in this Global Privacy Policy, we may share your personal data within the Movado Group and with external third parties. This may require a transfer of your personal data to the United States and to countries outside the country in which we originally collected the information. Those countries may not have the same data protection laws. When we transfer your information to other countries, we will protect that information as described in this Global Privacy Policy.

Consistent with its commitment to protect personal privacy, MGI has entered into agreements with its subsidiaries resident in the EEA and Switzerland to ensure that adequate protection be given to personal data transferred from the EEA and Switzerland to the United States. These agreements are based on “standard contractual clauses” promulgated by the EU and Swiss governments. Copies of the non-confidential provisions of these agreements are available by[ _Contacting us_](mailto:privacy@movadogroup.com).

When Movado Group transfers personal data to external third parties it obtains assurances that the information will be used consistently with this Global Privacy Policy. If the personal data from a resident of the EEA or Switzerland is transferred out of the EEA or Switzerland, then we ensure a similar degree of protection is afforded to it by implementing at least one of the following safeguards: (i) confirming that the European Commission has determined that the country provides an adequate level of protection for personal data; (ii) using specific contracts approved by the European Commission or Switzerland that give personal data the same level of protection it has in the EEA or Switzerland; (iii) using providers based in the transferee countries under arrangements approved by the European Commission, such as the Privacy Shield in the United States; or (iv) putting contractual provisions in place that provide appropriate data protections.

If you are a resident of the EEA or Switzerland, please [_Contact us_](mailto:privacy@movadogroup.com) if you want further information on the specific mechanism used by us when transferring your personal data out of the EEA or Switzerland.

### 7\. DATA SECURITY

We maintain administrative, technical, and physical safeguards designed to protect the personal data you provide against accidental, unlawful, or unauthorized destruction, loss, alteration, access, disclosure or use. While no safeguards are infallible, we take data security seriously and believe that we have implemented robust measures to minimize the risk of data breaches. However, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted over the internet, and we do no warrant the security of ay information, including personal data, which you transmit to us over the internet.

### 8\. DATA RETENTION

We will retain your personal data for as long as we believe it is needed to fulfill the purpose(s) we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, accounting, or reporting requirements. In some circumstances we may anonymize your personal data (so that it can no longer be associated with you) for analytical, statistical, or other purposes, in which case we may use or share this information indefinitely without further notice to you. Similarly, we may use or share Aggregated Data indefinitely without further notice to you. In general, we will retain your personal data for as long as we engage with you and, following that period, we will only retain your personal information for as long as is reasonably necessary under the circumstances.

Where the GDPR applies, you can ask us under certain circumstances to delete your data: see _Your Legal Rights Under the GDPR_ below for further information.

### 9\. YOUR RIGHTS AND CHOICES

We offer you certain choices in connection with the personal data we collect about you, such as how we communicate directly with you. To update your preferences, to ask us to remove you from our mailing lists, to exercise your rights, or to submit a request, please [_Contact us_](mailto:privacy@movadogroup.com). You can also unsubscribe from our mailing lists by following the “Unsubscribe” link in our emails.

To the extent permitted by law, you also may [_Contact us_](mailto:privacy@movadogroup.com) to request access to the personal data we maintain about you or request that we correct, amend, delete, or block the information.

If you are a resident of the EEA or of Switzerland, you have the right to make a complaint at any time to the European Data Protection Supervisor, to the Data Protection Authority in the applicable EU Member State, or to the Swiss Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner. A list of EEA authorities is available at [_http://ec.europa.eu/justice/article-29/structure/data-protection-authorities/index_en.htm_](http://ec.europa.eu/justice/article-29/structure/data-protection-authorities/index_en.htm). We would, however, appreciate the chance to respond to your concerns before you approach these governmental agencies, so please contact us in the first instance.

YOUR LEGAL RIGHTS UNDER THE GDPR

Where the GDPR applies, under certain circumstances you have rights in relation to your personal data, including the right to:

  * **Request access** to your personal data (commonly known as a “data subject access request”). This enables you to receive a copy of the personal data we hold about you and to check that we are lawfully processing it. If we provide you with access to the information we hold about you, we will not charge you unless permitted by law. If you request further copies of this data from us, we may charge you a reasonable administrative cost. Where we are legally permitted to do so, we may refuse your request. If we refuse your request we will tell you our reasons for doing so.
  * **Request correction** of the personal data that we hold about you. This enables you to have any incomplete or inaccurate data we hold about you corrected, though we may need to verify the accuracy of the new data you provide to us. If we have shared this personal data with third parties we will notify them about your correction request unless this is impossible or involves disproportionate effort. You also may request details of the third parties to whom we have disclosed the inaccurate or incomplete personal data. Where we think that it is reasonable for us not to comply with your request, we will explain our decision to you.
  * **Request erasure** of your personal data. This enables you to ask us to delete or remove personal data where there is no good reason for us continuing to process it. You also have the right to ask us to delete or remove your personal data where you have successfully exercised your right to object to processing (see below), where we may have processed your information unlawfully, or where we are required to erase your personal data to comply with local law. Note, however, that we may not always be able to comply with your request of erasure for specific legal reasons which will be notified to you, if applicable, at the time of your request.
  * **Object to processing** of your personal data where we are relying on a legitimate interest (or those of a third party) and there is something about your particular situation which makes you want to object to processing on this ground as you feel it impacts on your fundamental rights and freedoms. Where we are processing your personal data for direct marketing purposes you have the right to object to processing. You also have the right to object to processing in the event we do so to enable us to perform a task in the public interest or exercise official authority, or for scientific, historical, research, or statistical purposes. In some cases, we may demonstrate that we have compelling legitimate grounds to process your information which override your rights and freedoms.
  * **Request restriction of processing** of your personal data. This enables you to ask us to suspend the processing of your personal data in the following scenarios: (a) if you want us to establish the data’s accuracy; (b) where our use of the data is unlawful but you do not want us to erase it; (c) where you need us to hold the data even if we no longer require it as you need it to establish, exercise, or defend legal claims; or (d) you have objected to our use of your data but we need to verify whether we have overriding legitimate grounds to use it. If we have shared your personal data with third parties, unless it is impossible or involves disproportionate effort we will use reasonable efforts to notify them about your request to restrict processing.
  * **Request the transfer** of your personal data to you or to a third party. We will provide to you, or a third party you have chosen, your personal data in a structured, commonly used, machine-readable format. Note that this right only applies to automated information which you initially provided consent for us to use or where we used the information to perform a contract with you.
  * **Withdraw consent at any time** where we are relying on consent to process your personal data. However, this will not affect the lawfulness of any processing carried out before you withdraw your consent. If you withdraw your consent, we may not be able to provide certain products or services to you. We will advise you if this is the case at the time you seek to withdraw your consent. In the event you withdraw your consent, we will cease to use your data for that purpose unless we consider that there is an alternative legal basis to justify our continued processing of your information for this purpose, in which case we will inform you of this legal basis.

### 10\. COOKIES AND OTHER AUTOMATED MEANS

When you visit our websites, open our emails, use our apps or “smart” wearable devices, or interact with Movado Group-related social media sites or tools, widgets, or plug-ins, we may collect certain information by automated means, such as cookies, web beacons, and web server logs.

We use cookies and other automated means to optimize your user experience, the functionality of our website, and the products and services we offer. When you visit our sites or use our apps, tools, and devices, our web server sends a file to your computer, which allows us to recognize your computer to perform a variety of functions. More details about this are described below.

By proceeding to navigate through these mediums, you consent to our cookie settings and agree that you understand this section of our Global Privacy Policy pertaining to cookies.

WHAT ARE COOKIES, WEB BEACONS, AND OTHER AUTOMATED MEANS?

A “cookie” is a file that websites send to a visitor’s computer or other Internet-connected device to uniquely identify the visitor’s browser or to store information or settings in the browser. A “web beacon,” also known as an Internet tag, pixel tag, or clear GIF, links web pages to web servers and their cookies and may be used to transmit information collected through cookies back to a web server. Through these automated collection methods, we obtain “clickstream data,” which is a log of the links and other content on which a visitor clicks while browsing a website. As the visitor clicks through the website, a record of the action may be collected and stored. We may link certain data elements we have collected through automated means, such as your browser information, with other information we have obtained about you to let us know, for example, whether you have opened an email we sent to you.

WHAT PURPOSES DO AUTOMATED MEANS SERVE?

  1. Cookies Support Basic Website Functionality: Some cookies are functional and necessary cookies that support essential features of our website, such as storing your shopping cart selections while you continue to shop and navigate to different pages of our website. Functionality cookies also are used to recognize you when you return to our website. This enables us to personalize our content for you, greet you by name, and remember your preferences (for example, your choice of language or region). Cookies also help us direct consumers to their appropriate website and to determine whether an order is valid.
  2. Cookies Can Help Improve the Quality of Our Website and Services: Some cookies collect information to assess how you use our website so that we can improve the navigability of our site and provide you with better service. This is known as website analytics, and we use Google Analytics tools for this function. We use Analytics Cookies to: 
    * Provide aggregate and anonymous statistics on how our site is used;
    * See how effective our advertisements are by identifying where you click and from which website you arrived;
    * Provide feedback to carefully selected third party partners that one of our visitors also visited their website;
    * Help us improve the site by capturing errors in your browsing experience;
    * Provide you with improved site functionality by allowing access to additional services or restoring your shopping bag if you wish to return on a subsequent browsing session
  3. Cookies Allow Us to Personalize Your Experience: Certain cookies record your visit to our website, the pages you have visited, and the links you have followed. We use this information to make our website and the advertising displayed on it more relevant to your interests.
  4. Cookies May Share Information With Our Carefully Chosen Third-Party Partners: Aside from setting cookies ourselves, we also allow carefully-selected third parties to set cookies during your visit to our website. These organizations provide us with information on your use of the website. They also may use cookies to promote our newest products and latest offers to you on other websites. For example, you may see products you viewed on our website presented on other websites as you navigate the internet. Some of our partners will use your location to provide more relevant messaging.

WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT THROUGH COOKIES?

Most of the information captured by cookies or other automated means will not identify you personally. The data we collect through cookies and other automated means may include unique device identifier; browser characteristics; device characteristics; operating system; language preferences; referring URLs; information on actions taken on our site; dates and times of website visits, downloads, and activations. In certain circumstances we also may collect your IP address or data collected through usage of our apps and “smart” wearable devices, such as geolocation.

MANAGING YOUR COOKIE PREFERENCES

To manage third-party cookies served on our site, please visit Google Analytics: [_http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html_](http://www.google.com/analytics/learn/privacy.html). Through this link you may opt-out of some or all third-party cookies. This will not affect or disable the cookies served by the Movado Group.

To manage all cookies on our site, including those that are served by the Movado Group, you can change your browser settings. For additional information on how to manage all cookies please visit [_http://www.allaboutcookies.org/_](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). Please note that disabling, blocking, or deleting cookies in your browser settings may impact your ability to fully use both our website and other websites.

If you wish to disable the use of cookies on this website only, [_Click here_](https://www.movado.com/on/demandware.store/Sites-MovadoUS-Site/en_US/Util-ChangeTrackingStatus). Please note that activating this option will impact your ability to fully use this website.

Certain web browsers allow you to instruct your browser to send Do Not Track (“DNT”) signals to websites you visit, informing those sites that you do not want your online activities to be tracked. When we recognize a relevant DNT signal we aim to suppress the third-party tags that are used to recognize your computer once you navigate away from our site and which are used to present you with Movado Group advertisements. However, currently there is no uniform standard for DNT signal recognition, and our technology may not recognize all DNT signals. Thus, if you do not wish for cookies or other automated means to be enabled, we encourage you to manage cookies through the other means noted above.

On subsequent visits to this site after using one of the means noted above to manage your cookies settings you may be notified or asked if you wish to change your settings. You may change your elections by following the prompts or by agreeing to the use of cookies going forward.

### 11\. NOTICE TO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS

Subject to certain limitations under California Civil Code §1798.83, California residents may ask us to provide them with (i) a list of certain categories of personal information that we have disclosed to third parties for their direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year, and (ii) the identity of those third parties. To make this request, California residents may [_Contact us_](mailto:privacy@movadogroup.com).

### 12\. MOVADO GROUP COMPANIES THAT PROCESS AND SHARE PERSONAL DATA

We set forth below details of the Movado Group companies that process and share personal data.

When you visit one of our after sales service websites (mgiservice) you will be given directions about where to send your watch for service or repairs. The entity to which you are directed will be the controller of your personal data.

When you visit one of our other websites, the controller of your personal data will be as identified below.

_**UNITED STATES**_

**Movado Group, Inc.**  
650 From Road  
Ste. 375  
Paramus, NJ 07652  
[controller for US ecommerce and all non-ecommerce websites]

**Movado Retail Group, Inc**.  
650 From Road  
Ste. 375  
Paramus, NJ 07652

 _ **CANADA**_

**Movado Group of Canada Inc.**  
One Main Street West  
Hamilton, Ontario  
L8P 4Z5 Canada  
[controller for Canadian websites]

 _ **CHINA**_

**MGI Luxury Trading (Shanghai) Co., Ltd.**  
Room 20F02, Plaza 889  
1111 ChangShou Road  
Jing’an District  
Shanghai 200042  
Peoples Republic of China

 _ **FRANCE**_

**Movado Group France SAS**  
47 rue de la Chaussee d’Antin  
75009 Paris  
France  
[controller for French websites]

 _ **GERMANY**_

**MGI Luxury Group GmbH**  
Landsberger Str. 94  
80339 München  
Germany

**Movado Group Deutschland GmbH**  
Gartenstr. 97  
73431 Aalen  
Germany  
[controller for German websites]

 _ **HONG KONG**_

**Swissam Products Ltd.**  
5th Floor, Alexander House  
18 Charter Road  
Hong Kong

**MGI Luxury Asia Pacific Limited**  
29th Floor, Citicorp Centre  
18 Whitfield Road, North Point  
Hong Kong

 _ **MALAYSIA**_

**MGI Luxury Malaysia Sdn.Bhd.**  
Level 30, The Gardens North Tower  
Mid Valley City  
Lingkaran Syed Putra  
59200 Kuala Lumpur  
Malaysia

 _ **MEXICO**_

**MGI Distribución, S. de R.L. de C.V.**  
Torre Esmeralda III  
Blvd Manuel Ávila Camacho #32  
Piso 6 Oficina 687  
Col. Lomas de Chapultepec CP 11000  
Mexico

 _ **NETHERLANDS**_

**MGI Luxury Group B.V.**  
c/o Intertrust  
Prins Bernhardplein 200  
1097 JB Amsterdam  
The Netherlands

**Movado Group Nederland B.V.**  
c/o Intertrust  
Prins Bernhardplein 200  
1097 JB Amsterdam  
The Netherlands

 _ **SINGAPORE**_

**MGI Luxury Singpore Pte Ltd**  
#06-02 Tong Building  
302 Orchard Road  
Singapore 238862

 _ **SWITZERLAND**_

**Movado Watch Company SA**  
Bettlachstr. 8  
2540 Grenchen  
Switzerland

**MGI Luxury Group SA**  
Bahnhofplatz 2B  
2502 Biel/Bienne  
Switzerland

**Concord Watch Company SA**  
c/o MGI Luxury Group SA  
Bahnhofplatz 2B  
2502 Biel/Bienne  
Switzerland

**Ebel Watches SA**  
c/o MGI Luxury Group SA  
Bahnhofplatz 2B  
2502 Biel/Bienne  
Switzerland

 _ **UNITED KINGDOM**_

**MOVADO Group UK Limited**  
Meadway  
Haslemere  
Surrey  
GU27 1NN  
United Kingdom  
[controller for UK websites and Olivia Burton EU and International websites]
